freewillastrology.com 2018-12-15

# Free Will Astrology : Privacy Policy

  |   |   |  We don't appreciate it when the Web sites we visit abuse our privacy rights, so we pledge to never abuse yours. 

Freewillastrology.com's goal is to provide readers with the all of the astrological insight, savvy spirituality, and literate tomfoolery that they want and need. To do that, we may gather some general information about those who access our site. We may place a "cookie" in the browser files of a user's computer, which will enable us to determine the user's operating system, browser type and version, ISP, top-level domain -- such as .com .edu, etc. -- and other such general information. 

Users have the ability to configure their browsers to refuse acceptance of cookies, which are pieces of information that sites transfer to a user's hard drive for record-keeping purposes during each visit. Cookies -- which do not contain any personally identifying information -- are a standard industry technology. Cookies help readers by saving such information as passwords and editorial preferences on user hard drives. A cookie cannot pass on a computer virus, or even capture your e-mail address. 

Free Will Astrology will only collect personally identifying information that users voluntarily provide to us in registering for services (such as the free newsletter we send out each week), filling out surveys, or entering contests. If you consent at the time you provide us with your information, we may also use that personal information editorially -- to improve and customize our content -- or we may employ volunteered personal information for marketing and promotional purposes, and may provide that information and aggregate statistics to reputable, pre-screened organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. 

Submissions sent to Free Will Astrology in response to "homework assignments" and contests become the property of Rob Brezsny and Free Will Astrology, and may be published in a variety of formats at our discretion, including but not limited to newsletters, books, and the Free Will Astrology column and Web site. We reserve the right to edit such submissions for length, style, and content. Requests for anonymity will be honored with submissions; otherwise, reader names, screen names, or initials will be used. Please be sure to note your preference when sending to us. We are not responsible for unsolicited submission of any creative material. Users can revoke their consent at any time to stop their information from being used for marketing and promotional purposes by sending an e-mail request to [privacy@freewillastrology.com](mailto:privacy@freewillastrology.com) or they can simply opt not to register for special services, surveys, or contests. 

Freewillastrology.com will limit internal access of user information to employees responsible for conducting business with or responding to the queries of our readers. 

Web surfers should be aware that by voluntarily disclosing personal information on freewillastrology.com's -- or any other site's -- bulletin and posting boards, those details can easily be collected and employed by third parties. Collection of Personal Data from Free Will Astrology's Web site is not intended for or marketed to persons under the age of 18. Free Will Astrology does not collect or post information from children under the age of 13 ("children"). Children are not allowed to participate in contests. 

Although we encourage all sites to adopt appropriate privacy policies, this policy applies only to the freewillastrology.com domain. We do not control the privacy policies of our advertisers or any other sites we may link to.

|
